Pamela Digby Churchill Hayward Harriman Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Subject File, 1968-1993 (Box II:1-II:79)
  - Boschwitz, Rudy, 1984, (2 folders)
  - Bowles, John, IV, 1984-1987
  - Boxer, Barbara, 1991
  - Bradley, Bill, 1978, 1991
  - Brown, Clarence J., study, 1982 (Box II:5)
  - Brown, Jean, 1990-1991
  - Brown, Ronald Harmon, 1988-1991, (2 folders)
  - Bumpers, Dale, 1987
  - Burdick, Quentin N., 1987
  - Bush, George H. W., 1988-1989
  - California, 1983-1985
  - Campaign finance
    - Congressional Research Service packet, 1986-1989, (2 folders)
    - Democratic versus Republican spending, 1979-1981
    - General
      - 1987-1990
      - 1990, undated (Box II:6)
    - State-by-state overview of laws, 1985, (2 folders)
    - State law compliance, 1981
  - Campaign techniques, 1980-1982
  - Center for Democratic Policy, 1981-1982
  - Center for National Policy, 1982-1989
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, 1990-1992
  - Citizen Action, 1983-1989, (2 folders) (Box II:7)
  - Citizens for Common Sense in National Defense, 1982
  - Citizens' Research Foundation, 1984-1989
  - Clifford, Clark M.
    - Bank of Credit and Commerce International, 1991-1992, (3 folders)
    - General, 1983-1989
  - Clinton, Bill
    - 1992 campaign
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1991-1992, (2 folders)
      - Mailings, 1992 (Box II:8)
      - Press, 1991-1992
      - Speeches by Clinton, 1991-1992
      - Talking points, 1992
    - Statements during early presidency, 1993, (2 folders)
    - Transition and inauguration, 1992-1993, (2 folders); (6 folders) (Box II:9)
  - Cochran, Thad, survey report, 1985, (2 folders) (Box II:10)
  - Commission on National Elections, 1985, (4 folders)
  - Commission on Presidential Debates (Box II:11)
    - 1987-1989, (7 folders)
    - 1990-1991, (6 folders) (Box II:12)
    - 1992, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:13)
    - 1993
  - Committee for American Principles, 1979-1982
  - Common Cause, 1989 (Box II:14)
  - Conrad, Kent, 1986
  - Conservative Democratic Forum, 1981
  - Conta, Dennis J., 1987
  - Cook Political Report, 1986
  - Corporate political action, 1980, 1987
  - Council for a Livable World, 1982-1984
  - Council on Competitiveness, 1991
  - C-Span, 1986-1989
  - Cuomo, Mario M.
    - Foreign policy advice memorandum, 1986
    - General, 1983-1991, (3 folders)
  - Daschle, Thomas, 1986
  - Democracy Project, 1987
  - Democratic communications meeting, Rayburn House Office Building, Washington, D.C., 1990
  - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee
    - Democratic Media Center, 1985 (Box II:15)
    - General
      - 1974-1987, (7 folders)
      - 1988-1991 (Box II:16)
    - Harriman Communications Center
      - 1986, (3 folders)
      - 1987
        - Jan.-Sept., (4 folders)
        - Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box II:17)
      - 1988-1990, (3 folders)
      - 1991, (1 folder) (Box II:18)
    - Mailings, 1980-1982
    - Post-election survey, 1980
  - Democratic Governors' Association
    - 1982-1989, (4 folders)
    - 1990-1993, (5 folders) (Box II:19)
  - Democratic House and Senate Council, 1978-1990, (5 folders) (Box II:20)
  - Democratic Issues Conference, White Sulphur Springs, W.Va., 1986
  - Democratic Leadership Council
    - 1985-1988
    - 1990-1992 (Box II:21)
  - Democratic message, 1986-1989
  - Democratic National Committee
    - Board of directors meetings, 1985-1986, (2 folders)
    - Building fund, 1968, 1980-1982
    - Business Council
      - 1984-1986, (2 folders)
      - 1987-1991 (Box II:22)
    - Calendars, 1983-1986
    - Chair selection, 1984-1985
    - Charter and bylaws, 1984-1988
    - Committee to Elect Democratic Governors, 1982, (2 folders)
    - Executive committee meeting, Oct. 28, 1983
    - General (Box II:23)
      - 1975-1986, (6 folders)
      - 1987-1993, (6 folders) (Box II:24)
    - Leadership Summit, Middleburg, Va., 1991, (2 folders)
    - Meeting with Charles T. Manatt, 1982 (Box II:25)
    - Policy reports, 1982-1992, (3 folders)
    - Presidential and Democratic Victory Fund, 1987-1988, (3 folders)
    - Presidential Sweep, 1983
    - Professional Services Program, undated (Box II:26)
    - Project 500
      - 1985-1986, (6 folders)
      - 1986-1990, (4 folders) (Box II:27)
    - Treasurer position, 1983
    - Trustees, 1988-1992, (2 folders)
    - Women's Council, 1983-1984
  - Democratic National Convention (Box II:28)
    - 1980, New York, N.Y.
    - 1984, San Francisco, Calif.
      - Binders, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:29)
      - Delegate selection process
      - Miscellany
      - Site selection
        - San Francisco, Calif., bid
        - Washington, D.C., bid See also Part II: Oversize, (1 folder); (10 folders) (Box II:30)
    - 1988, Atlanta, Ga. (Box II:31)
      - Binder
      - Democratic National News Network proposal
      - Miscellany
      - Site selection, Washington, D.C., bid, (2 folders)
    - 1992, New York, N.Y.
      - Communications, (1 folder) (Box II:32)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - IBM information system technology proposal
  - Democratic National Data Bank proposal, 1985 (Box II:33)
  - Democratic National Party Conference, Philadelphia, Pa., 1982
    - Democratic Fact Book press conference, (5 folders)
    - Event planning binder
    - Howard, Janet A., packets
    - Itineraries, arrangements, and notes (Box II:34)
    - Press clippings
    - Proceedings and other printed conference material
    - Speeches
  - Democratic Party future, 1979-1981, (3 folders)
  - Democratic political action committees, 1981-1982, (1 folder) (Box II:35)
  - Democratic political speeches, 1985
  - Democratic proposals, 1981-1982
  - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee
    - Briefing binders
      - 1982, 1988, (2 folders)
      - 1989, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:36)
      - 1990, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:37)
    - General
      - 1979-1987, (4 folders)
      - 1988-1992, (6 folders) (Box II:38)
  - Democratic Study Group, 1981-1982 (Box II:39)
  - Democrats Abroad, 1986-1991
  - "The Democrats and a New Grand Strategy: Part II," World Policy, 1986
  - Democrats for New Direction, 1989-1992
  - Democrats, general, 1981-1982
  - Diller, Barry, 1990
  - Dixon, Alan J., undated
  - Dolan Report, 1984
  - Dukakis, Michael S., 1988 See also Part II: Oversize
  - Economic Policy Institute, 1987-1991
  - Election-year data
    - 1980
    - 1982
      - Binders
        - Election analysis and political action committee contributions
        - Election and Ninety-eighth Congress outlook (Box II:40)
        - Election night
      - Files, (3 folders)
    - 1984, (2 folders)
    - 1986 (Box II:41)
      - Binders
        - For July board meeting
        - For fall board meeting
        - Senate and gubernatorial races
      - Files, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:42)
    - 1988
      - General background
      - Gubernatorial races
      - House races (Box II:43)
        - Alabama-Hawaii, (3 folders)
        - Illinois-Michigan, (3 folders) (Box II:44)
        - Minnesota-New Mexico (Box II:45)
        - New York-South Carolina, (3 folders) (Box II:46)
        - Tennessee-Washington state, (3 folders) (Box II:47)
      - News clippings, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box II:48, Box II:49)
      - Presidential candidates, (2 folders)
      - Presidential race, general (Box II:50)
      - Senate races
        - By state
          - Alabama-Mississippi, (2 folders)
          - Missouri-Wyoming, (3 folders) (Box II:51)
        - General (Box II:52)
      - State files
        - Alabama-Iowa, (2 folders)
        - Kentucky-Wisconsin and Puerto Rico, (3 folders) (Box II:53)
    - 1990
      - Gubernatorial races
        - By state
          - Alabama-Colorado
          - Florida-Wisconsin, (4 folders) (Box II:54)
        - General background (Box II:55)
      - House races
        - Alabama-Louisiana, (4 folders)
        - Maine-Wyoming, (4 folders) (Box II:56)
      - Mayoral race, District of Columbia (Box II:57)
      - Miscellaneous races
      - News clippings
      - Senate races
        - By state
          - Alabama-Kentucky, (2 folders)
          - Maine-West Virginia, (3 folders) (Box II:58)
        - General background, (2 folders) (Box II:59)
  - Emily's List, 1985-1992, (2 folders)
  - Energy, 1981
  - Environment, 1989-1991
  - Evans, Lane, 1982
  - Evans-Novak Political Report and Tax Report, 1980-1988 (Box II:60)
  - Farley, William, 1989
  - Federal Election Commission, 1976-1992, (2 folders)
  - Ferraro, Geraldine, 1984-1992
  - Fingerhut Granados Opinion Research, 1980-1988, (2 folders)
  - Flanagan, Daniel V., Jr., "What's on Americans' Minds?," 1987 (Box II:61)
  - Foley, Thomas S., 1988-1990
  - Foreign affairs, 1983-1992
  - Former members of Congress letter, 1980-1981
  - Foundation for Public Affairs, 1987-1988
  - Foundation for Women's Resources, 1988
  - Frank, Barney, 1982
  - Garvey, Ed, 1986
  - Gephardt, Richard A., 1985-1990
  - Germond Witcover Political Report, 1982-1984
  - Get-out-the-vote program proposals, 1981-1986
  - Glenn, John
    - 1981-1982
    - 1982 (Box II:62)
  - Gojack, Mary, 1980
  - Gore, Al
    - 1985-1988, (6 folders)
    - 1989-1992 (Box II:63)
  - Governors, 1981, 1987
  - Group Research Report, 1981
  - Growe, Joan Anderson, 1984
  - Hamilton, Lee H., 1987-1988
  - Handgun control, 1991
  - Harkin, Tom, 1984-1990
  - Harris, Janet, master's thesis incorporating Democrats for the 80's polling data, 1990
  - Hart, Gary, 1980-1987 (Box II:64)
  - Hatch, Orrin G., 1980-1982
  - Hay, Jess, 1983-1984
  - Health, 1988
  - Hightower, Jim, 1982-1987
  - Hischhorn, Susan B., 1981-1982
  - Hispanics, 1981-1983
  - Holtzman, Elizabeth, 1979, 1987
  - House of Representatives, 1980-1992
  - Howard, Frances, 1982, 1990
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund, undated
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., III, ("Skip"), 1987-1988
  - Idaho, 1985-1990 (Box II:65)
  - Illinois, 1981-1982
  - IMPAC 2000, 1988-1991
  - Independent Action, 1981-1992
  - John O'Donnell Co., 1987
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1972, 1981-1986
  - Kennedy, John F., quotation, undated
  - Kerrey, Robert, 1982, 1989-1990
  - Labor
    - 1980-1982, (2 folders)
    - 1982-1990, (3 folders) (Box II:66)
  - LaRouche, Lyndon H., 1981-1986 See also Part II: Oversize, (3 folders)
  - Leadership America, 1987-1988
  - League of Women Voters, 1984-1989
  - Lee, Chesie, 1986
  - Legislative checklist, 1986
  - Lewis, Steve, 1991 (Box II:67)
  - Licht, Richard A., 1987
  - McCurdy, Dave, 1991
  - McGovern, George, Americans for Common Sense, 1981-1982
  - McIntyre, Thomas J., 1978-1980
  - Media, 1987-1991, undated
  - Miller, Emilie, 1987
  - Milliken, John G., 1986
  - Minnesota, 1991
  - Mississippi, 1984-1987
  - Mitchell, George J., 1989
  - Mondale, Walter F.
    - Committee for the Future of America, 1982
    - Presidential campaign, 1983-1984, (2 folders)
  - Mother Jones, 1987-1989
  - Mrazek, Robert J., 1990-1992 (Box II:68)
  - Nader, Ralph, undated
  - National Center for Policy Alternatives, 1986-1989
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress, 1979-1989, (2 folders)
  - National Congressional Club, 1983
  - National Conservative Political Action Committee, 1981-1984, (2 folders)
  - National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, 1988-1990
  - National-House Democratic Caucus, 1983
  - National Lawyers Council, Democratic Fact Book, 1988 (Box II:69)
  - National Legislative Education Foundation, 1991
  - National Policy Exchange, 1982
  - National Women's Educational Fund, 1978-1982
  - National Women's Political Caucus, 1984-1987
  - Neighbor to Neighbor, 1988
  - New Democratic Dimensions, 1987-1991
  - New Mexico, 1982
  - New York, 1986-1987
  - New York Times Information Service, 1981
  - Niedermeier, Christine, 1987
  - Nuclear Freeze Foundation, 1982
  - "Nut" file, 1989-1990
  - Ohio, 1979, 1985-1986
  - Open Challenge Candidate Fund, 1990 Democratic Fact Book, 1988-1990
  - PAC Group, 1981-1982 (Box II:70)
  - Panama Freedom Foundation, 1988
  - Parker-Coltrane Political Action Committee, 1981-1982
  - PeacePAC, 1988-1990
  - People for the American Way, 1981-1983, 1990-1992
  - Perle, Richard, 1987
  - Political action committees
    - Business strategy, 1982
    - General, 1980-1989
    - Georgetown University Law Center, Washington, D.C., workshop, 1983
  - Political Animal newsletter by Joe Scott, 1985-1990
  - Political articles, speeches, and newsletters, 1969-1993, (3 folders) (Box II:71)
  - Political consultants and services, 1979-1990, undated, (2 folders)
  - Political database development, 1983
  - Political party reform, 1981
  - Politics, People, and Issues Report, 1981-1983
  - Polling, 1982-1991 (Box II:72)
  - Polling Report, Inc.
    - Newsletter, 1987-1990
    - "Political Day" news summaries, 1987-1988
  - Polls
    - 1983-1992, (4 folders)
    - Undated (Box II:73)
  - Post-election analysis form, 1981
  - Presidential speeches, undated
  - Progressive Policy Institute, 1989-1990
  - Progressive Political Action Committee, 1981-1982
  - Project Vote, 1984-1992
  - Public financing of state elections, 1986
  - Public Media Center, 1987-1988
  - Public Policy Analysis, 1986
  - Public Service Satellite Consortium, 1986
  - Renewing Congress report, 1992 (Box II:74)
  - Republican Party, 1980-1989
  - Riegle, Donald W., Jr., 1977
  - Robb, Charles S., 1989-1990
  - Rockefeller, John D., IV, 1991
  - Roe v. Wade, 1992
  - Schenk, Lynn, 1992
  - Seminars, 1981
  - Senate retreat, Easton, Md., 1982
  - Senior PAC, 1982
  - Severns, Penny, 1986
  - Simon, Paul (1928-2003), 1982
  - Southern Political Report, 1982-1990, (4 folders)
  - State of the Union addresses, 1983, 1988
  - Strategic Defense Initiative ("Star Wars"), 1985 (Box II:75)
  - Teamwork Economics, 1987-1991
  - Texas, 1983-1990
  - Texas women, 1988-1989
  - Thomas, Clarence, 1991
  - Times Mirror Co. surveys
    - 1988-1990, (3 folders)
    - 1990-1991 (Box II:76)
  - University of Southern California, Washington Politics Program, 1985
  - U.S. Newswire, 1987-1988
  - U.S. Senate Democratic Leadership Circle, 1981-1990, (2 folders)
  - USA Votes, 1987-1988
  - Vermont Voter File, 1986-1987
  - Virginia, 1982-1992, undated, (2 folders)
  - Voters for Choice, 1982-1991
  - Ward, Tom, 1987
  - Washington Resources and Strategy, 1987-1988
  - Wealthy business elite, 1988
  - Western States Strategy Center, 1987 (Box II:77)
  - Winpisinger, William W., 1986-1988
  - Wisconsin, 1985-1988
  - Wofford, Harris, 1991
  - Wolf, Scott, 1978-1981
  - Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
    - 1971-1991, (5 folders)
    - 1991-1992, (3 folders) (Box II:78)
  - Woman's Suburban Democratic Club, Montgomery Co., Md., 1981
  - Women, 1981-1992, (2 folders)
  - Women Making History, 1984-1985
  - Women's Campaign Fund, 1979, 1988
  - Women's Information Network, 1990-1992
  - Women's races, 1992
  - Women's vote analysis, 1985 (Box II:79)
  - Woods, Harriett, 1982-1990
- Part II: Administrative File, 1973-1993 (Box II:79-II:140)
  Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, proposals, resolutions, financial and legal records, a corporate seal, Federal Election Commission filings, brochures and newsletters, transcripts of events and meetings, press contact lists and talking points, other lists and card files, procedural manuals, notes, and printed matter documenting many aspects of the founding, activities, operations, and eventual dissolution of the Democrats for the 80's (Democrats for the 90's after 1989).
  - Acknowledgment letters, 1982, 1989, (2 folders) (Box II:79)
  - Advisory and finance committees, 1980-1981
  - Board of directors and executive committee lists, 1981-circa 1990
  - Breakfast briefings, 1982
  - Brochures
    - Master file, 1981-1989
    - Writing and design, 1981-1989, (4 folders)
  - Buttons and other campaign product catalogs, 1981-1990
  - Bylaws and articles of incorporation, 1980-1981 (Box II:80)
  - Chronological file
    - 1980
      - Correspondence, (2 folders)
      - Founding of the Democrats for the 80's, (4 folders)
    - 1981
      - Board minutes
      - Correspondence
        - Alphabetical file
          - A-C, (3 folders)
          - D-O, (11 folders) (Box II:81)
          - P-Z, (7 folders) (Box II:82)
        - Chronological file
          - Jan.-Apr., (4 folders)
          - Apr.-Oct., (8 folders) (Box II:83)
          - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box II:84)
      - Financial records
      - Meetings, (4 folders)
      - Memoranda, (3 folders)
      - Outreach letters (Box II:85)
      - Political contributions
      - Strategy
    - 1982
      - Binder, (2 folders)
      - Board minutes
      - Correspondence
        - Alphabetical file
          - A-G, (7 folders)
          - H-W, (9 folders) (Box II:86)
        - Chronological file
          - Jan.-May, (5 folders)
          - June-Dec., (7 folders) (Box II:87)
      - Financial records
      - Meetings, (4 folders)
      - Memoranda, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:88)
      - Outreach letters
      - Political contributions, (2 folders)
      - Subcommittee on candidate support
    - 1983 (Box II:89)
      - Annual report
      - Briefing packet
      - Binder, "Chron. Book"
      - Correspondence
        - Feb.-Sept., (8 folders)
        - Oct.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box II:90)
      - Financial records
      - Meetings, (2 folders)
      - Memoranda, (2 folders)
      - Political contributions
    - 1984
      - Annual report and meeting
      - Calendar
      - Financial records
      - Memoranda
      - Political contributions (Box II:91)
        - File for 1984
        - Summary of 1982-1984
    - 1985
      - Correspondence
        - Mar.-July, (5 folders)
        - July, (3 folders) (Box II:92)
      - Financial records, (2 folders)
      - Meetings, (2 folders)
      - Memoranda
      - Political contributions (Box II:93)
    - 1986
      - Correspondence, (2 folders)
      - Financial records, (2 folders)
      - Meetings, (3 folders)
      - Memoranda (Box II:94)
      - Political contributions, (3 folders)
    - 1987
      - Correspondence
        - Jan.-Sept., (3 folders)
        - Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box II:95)
      - Financial records
      - Memoranda
      - Political contributions
    - 1988
      - Correspondence
        - Alphabetical file
          - A-N, (13 folders)
          - O-Z, (6 folders) (Box II:96)
        - Chronological file
          - Jan.-Oct., (9 folders)
          - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box II:97)
      - Financial records
      - Memoranda
      - Political contributions, (3 folders)
    - 1989
      - Correspondence
        - Alphabetical file
          - A-E, (4 folders)
          - F-W, (7 folders) (Box II:98)
        - Chronological file, (2 folders)
      - Financial records
      - Memoranda
      - Political contributions
    - 1990
      - Correspondence
        - Alphabetical file, (2 folders)
        - Chronological file
          - Jan.-June
          - July-Dec. (Box II:99)
      - Decision to dissolve the Democrats for the 90's
      - Financial records
      - Meeting
      - Memoranda
      - Political contributions
    - 1991-1992, (2 folders)
    - 1993, political contributions by Harriman with summary report for 1987-1992
  - Computers, 1981-1989, (3 folders) (Box II:100)
  - Congressional liaison committee, 1981
  - Contributor information handout, 1986, undated
  - Contributors
    - Card file, 1979-1980 See Part II: Oversize
    - Miscellaneous lists
      - 1980-1984, (4 folders)
      - 1985-1986, (5 folders) (Box II:101)
      - 1987, (1 folder) (Box II:102)
      - 1989-1990, undated, (2 folders)
    - Potential, 1985
  - Corporate seal, 1981
  - District of Columbia annual corporate report, 1981-1990
  - Event planning
    - General, 1983-1986
    - Tents, 1982-1986
  - Executive director
    - 1981-1982
    - 1983-1985, (2 folders) (Box II:103)
  - Faxes, 1989-1992, (7 folders)
  - Federal Election Commission reports
    - 1980
    - 1981-1982, (8 folders) (Box II:104)
    - 1983, (4 folders) (Box II:105)
    - 1984, (3 folders) (Box II:106)
    - 1985, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:107)
    - 1986, (5 folders); (3 folders) (Box II:108)
    - 1987-1988, (4 folders)
    - 1989-1991, (4 folders) (Box II:109)
  - Federal Express log, 1984
  - File copies of mailings, brochures, and newsletters, 1981-1982, (2 folders)
  - File system, 1982-1987
  - Financial ledgers, 1981-1985 See also Part II: Oversize, (1 folder) (Box II:110)
  - Financial planning, 1979-1983, (2 folders)
  - Form letters, 1981
  - Forms, 1985, undated
  - Fund-raising plans, 1980-1983, (3 folders)
  - Haley, Riitta
    - Event synopsis book, 1984-1985
    - Letters and memoranda, 1982-1983, (3 folders) (Box II:111)
    - Memoranda, 1980-1985
  - Howard, Janet A.
    - Calendars, 1979-1980, 1992, (2 folders)
    - Chronological file
      - 1978-1980, (2 folders)
      - 1981, (2 folders); (6 folders) (Box II:112)
      - 1982, (6 folders)
      - 1983, (2 folders); (9 folders) (Box II:113)
      - 1984, (8 folders)
      - 1985, (15 folders) (Box II:114)
      - 1986, (2 folders); (7 folders) (Box II:115)
      - 1987, (9 folders); (4 folders) (Box II:116)
      - 1988, (11 folders)
      - 1989, (16 folders) (Box II:117)
      - 1990, (17 folders); (16 folders); (12 folders) (Box II:118, Box II:119, Box II:120)
      - 1991, (1 folder); (9 folders) (Box II:121)
      - 1992, (3 folders); (12 folders); (15 folders); (11 folders) (Box II:122, Box II:123, Box II:124)
      - 1993, (2 folders)
      - Undated, (2 folders); (6 folders) (Box II:125)
    - Notes, largely by her, 1980s-1990s, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:126)
    - Rolodex, photocopy, undated
  - Insurance and liability, 1982
  - Interns, 1985-1990
  - Issue evenings
    - General, 1981-1987, (2 folders)
    - Major donors, 1985
    - Procedures, 1985
    - Sample letters, 1985
    - Schedules, 1981-1990 (Box II:127)
  - Key contributor list, undated
  - Legal file, 1980-1993, (4 folders)
  - Letterhead and stationery, 1980s-1990s
  - Logo, 1980s
  - Napolitan, Joseph, program evaluation and recommendations, 1988-1989
  - National Bank of Washington, lockbox agreement, 1981-1982
  - Newsletter (Box II:128)
    - File copies, 1981-1988
    - Mailing lists, 1986-1988
    - Production materials
      - 1981-1986, (9 folders)
      - 1986-1988, (6 folders) (Box II:129)
      - 1988, (2 folders) (Box II:130)
    - Samples and models, 1982-1985
  - Non-federal program proposals, 1984-1985, (2 folders)
  - Non-federal reporting
    - 1982-1983, (2 folders)
    - 1984-1986, (6 folders) (Box II:131)
    - 1986-1988, (5 folders) (Box II:132)
    - 1988-1989, (4 folders) (Box II:133)
    - 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box II:134)
    - 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box II:135)
  - Office
    - Memoranda
      - 1980-1986, (7 folders)
      - 1988-1993, (2 folders) (Box II:136)
    - Operational binder, 1981-1985
    - Procedures, 1982-1986, undated, (2 folders)
    - Rental agreements, 1982-1990, (2 folders)
    - Security, 1985-1986
  - Photographers, 1980-1982
  - Political Christmas card, 1982-1983, 1990
  - Post office, 1981-1985
  - Press (Box II:137)
    - Contacts and lists, 1980-1985, (2 folders)
    - Political biography of Pamela Harriman, 1986-1992
    - Sample press kits, 1982-1985
    - Talking points
      - 1980-1986, (5 folders)
      - 1987-1992 (Box II:138)
  - Resolutions of the board of directors, 1981-1983, 1989
  - Sample invitations, 1984-1988
  - Sample letters, 1981-1983, (3 folders)
  - Schedules
    - Driver and pilot, 1986
    - Pantry, 1982-1990, (2 folders)
    - Staff
      - 1985
      - 1986-1990 (Box II:139)
  - Staffing and staff lists, 1982-1986
  - Tax-exempt research and education organization proposal, 1973-1981
  - Telemarketing, 1985-1987
  - To-do lists, 1990
  - Transcripts of events and meetings, 1981-1983, (3 folders)
  - Vendors
    - 1985-1987
    - 1988-1991, undated, (3 folders) (Box II:140)